Alright folks, next we're going to talk about footwear and shoes you can have to complete your vintage look.
Now the downside, I think, to looking for vintage footwear is in my case, maybe not in all cases, is they tend to be a lot of small sizes, kind of narrow, and a lot of them are hard to find in really good condition.
I think just because shoes tend to get a lot of wear and tear as opposed to a vintage dress that someone might wear a handful of times.
The shoes, again get a little wear and tear.
But you're still going to be able to find some cute ones out there.
Now, one type of vintage shoe that I absolutely love and a lot of vintage know hower's out there know they're really fun.
They look junky from a distance, but they're pretty darn cute.
These ones here, just like some little plastic patent ones.
But, when you look closely, these just have amazing detail.
These ones have a loose heel on them and you can see the detailing that they have on them, just rhinestones are lined down the back of these.
Just amazing.
Unfortunately, as cute as these are, you're going to find a lot of the missing rhinestones on there and for this one, the insole's got torn out.
It's just really cute, but what I need to do is go to my craft store, pick up some rhinestones and just kind of fix them back in there.
The vintage shoes sometimes, they just need a little more help.
Especially the fancier ones like this.
So these one's have some potential, but I might want to bring into a shoe store to get some insoles in here and then maybe have them or myself just maybe hot glue back in some or super glue back in, some little rhinestones in there.
But what you can do is, an alternative to finding some cute vintage themed shoes is you're going to want to try to find some modern day shoes with a vintage look and there's a lot of them out there.
Now, Ebay has been a great source for me to find some modern shoes that are priced really affordable but that maintain the integrity of a vintage shoe.
Here's one pair that I found.
They look great.
They look vintage.
Just these ones are modern and it's great because you're going to find your size.
They're brand new and you know, they just look really cute.
They look like they could be a vintage with some great detailing on them.
And here's another pair. They don't look quite as vintage. They have a vintage flair to them. But just look for bows, look for prints, like the polk-a-dots and what not, looks for the nice heels like that.
These are going to last you longer.
They're going to be a little more affordable and they're going to be a lot more comfortable to create that vintage outfit for you and tie it all together.
Now, you might be lucky out there and find some vintage shoes that are in great condition.
So you know, when you go to the stores, don't neglect the shoe section.
Go and take a peek.
You might find something.
But you're best bet, I think sometimes might be to just look online or just look in your shops for some vintage replica shoes and that there is some great tips on finding some vintage footwear to help round out and complete your vintage look.